export const data = [
    {
        question: "What is React.js ?",
        option1: "Framework",
        option2: "Library",
        option3: "Scripting Language",
        option4: "Database",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "The function which is called to render HTML to a web page in React ?",
        option1: "ReactDOM_render()",
        option2: "render()",
        option3: "render_DOM()",
        option4: "DOM_HTML()",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Total ways of defining variables in ES6 is ?",
        option1: "1",
        option2: "2",
        option3: "3",
        option4: "4",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What is ReactJS primarily used for ?",
        option1: "Database",
        option2: "User Interfaces",
        option3: "Connectivity",
        option4: "Design platform",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Which company developed React.jS ?",
        option1: "Google",
        option2: "Facebook",
        option3: "Microsoft",
        option4: "Apple",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following are the two ways to handle data in React ?",
        option1: "State and Functions",
        option2: "Props and Variables",
        option3: "Props and State",
        option4: "Variables and Functions",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the default port number in which the application run ?",
        option1: "3030",
        option2: "8000",
        option3: "5000",
        option4: "3000",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "In React.js, how we can pass the data from one component to another in React.js ?",
        option1: "Props",
        option2: "State",
        option3: "Variables",
        option4: "Functions",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following method is true about referring parent class in React.js ?",
        option1: "self()",
        option2: "inherits()",
        option3: "this()",
        option4: "super()",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the best definition of React.js ?",
        option1: "Server-side framework",
        option2: "User-interface framework",
        option3: "A library for building interaction interfaces",
        option4: "None of these",
        ans: 3,
    }
];